<resources>
    <string name="jamesE">
    James Gosling received a Bachelor of Science from the University of Calgary and his M.A. and Ph.D. from Carnegie Mellon University, all in computer science. He wrote a version of Emacs called Gosling Emacs (Gosmacs) while working toward his doctorate. He built a multi-processor version of Unix for a 16-way computer system. while at Carnegie Mellon University, before joining Sun Microsystems. He also developed several compilers and mail systems there.Gosling was with Sun Microsystems between 1984 and 2010 (26 years). He is known as the father of the Java programming language. He got the idea for the Java VM while writing a program to port software from a PERQ by translating Perq Q-Code to VAX assembler and emulating the hardware. He left Sun Microsystems on April 2, 2010 after it was acquired by the Oracle Corporation, citing reductions in pay, status, and decision-making ability, along with change of role and ethical challenges. He has since taken a very critical stance towards Oracle in interviews, noting that "during the integration meetings between Sun and Oracle, where we were being grilled about the patent situation between Sun and Google, we could see the Oracle lawyer\'s eyes sparkle." He clarified his position during the Oracle v Google trial over Android: "While I have differences with Oracle, in this case, they are on the right. Google totally slimed Sun. We were all really disturbed, even Jonathan Schwartz; he just decided to put on a happy face and tried to turn lemons into lemonade, which annoyed a lot of folks on Sun." However, he approved of the court\'s ruling that APIs should not be copyrightable.In March 2011, Gosling left Oracle to work at Google. Six months later, he followed his colleague Bill Vass and joined a startup called Liquid Robotics. In late 2016, Liquid Robotics was acquired by Boeing. Following the acquisition, Gosling left Liquid Robotics to work at Amazon Web Services as Distinguished Engineer in May 2017.He is an adviser at the Scala company Lightbend, Independent Director at Jelastic, and Strategic Advisor for Eucalyptus, and is a board member of DIRTT Environmental Solutions.
</string>
    <string name="adaE" >
    Augusta Ada King, Countess of Lovelace ( 10 December 1815-27 November 1852) was an English mathematician and writer, chiefly known for her work on Charles Babbage\'s proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine. She was the first to recognise that the machine had applications beyond pure calculation, and published the first algorithm intended to be carried out by such a machine. As a result, she is sometimes regarded as the first to recognise the full potential of a "computing machine" and one of the first computer programmers.Lovelace was the only legitimate child of the poet Lord Byron and his wife Anne Isabella "Annabella" Milbanke, Lady Wentworth. All of Byron\'s other children were born out of wedlock to other women. Byron separated from his wife a month after Ada was born and left England forever four months later. He commemorated the parting in a poem that begins, "Is thy face like thy mother\'s my fair child! ADA! sole daughter of my house and heart?". He died of disease in the Greek War of Independence when Ada was eight years old. Her mother remained bitter and promoted Ada\'s interest in mathematics and logic in an effort to prevent her from developing her father\'s perceived insanity. Despite this, Ada remained interested in Byron and was, upon her eventual death, buried next to him at her request. She was often ill in her childhood. Ada married William King in 1835. King was made Earl of Lovelace in 1838, Ada thereby becoming Countess of Lovelace.
 </string>
    <string name="jamesC" >
    James Gosling获得了卡尔加里大学的理学学士学位和卡内基梅隆大学的硕士和博士学位，都是计算机科学。在攻读博士学位期间，他编写了一个名为Gosling Emacs (Gosmacs)的Emacs版本。他为16路计算机系统构建了一个多处理器版本的Unix在卡内基梅隆大学，加入Sun微系统公司之前。他还在那里开发了几个编译器和邮件系统。高斯林在1984年到2010年间(26年)在太阳微系统公司工作。他被称为Java编程语言之父。他在编写从PERQ移植软件的程序时，通过将PERQ q代码转换为VAX汇编程序并模拟硬件，产生了Java VM的想法。2010年4月2日，在Sun被甲骨文公司收购后，他离开了Sun微系统公司。[8]称，该公司的薪酬、地位和决策能力都有所下降，同时角色也发生了变化，面临道德挑战。此后，他在采访中对甲骨文采取了非常关键的立场，指出“在Sun和甲骨文的整合会议上，我们被问及Sun和谷歌之间的专利情况，我们可以看到甲骨文律师的眼睛闪闪发光。”在甲骨文诉谷歌安卓案的庭审中，他澄清了自己的立场:“虽然我和甲骨文有分歧，但在这件事上，他们是对的。谷歌完全粘住了太阳。我们都很不安，甚至乔纳森·施瓦茨;他只是决定装出一副高兴的样子，试着把柠檬变成柠檬汁，这惹恼了Sun的很多人。”然而，他赞同法院关于api不应享有版权的裁决。2011年3月，高斯林离开甲骨文，来到谷歌工作。六个月后，他跟随同事比尔·瓦斯(Bill Vass)加入了一家名为液体机器人(Liquid Robotics)的初创公司。2016年末，液态机器人被波音公司收购。收购完成后，高斯林于2017年5月离开液体机器人公司，到亚马逊网络服务公司(Amazon Web Services)担任杰出工程师。他是Scala公司Lightbend的顾问，Jelastic的独立董事，Eucalyptus的战略顾问，DIRTT Environmental Solutions的董事会成员
</string>
    <string name="adaC">
     奥古斯塔·阿达·金，洛夫莱斯伯爵夫人(内拜伦;1815年12月10日- 1852年11月27日)，英国数学家和作家，主要以研究查尔斯·巴贝奇提出的通用机械计算机——分析引擎而闻名。她是第一个认识到这台机器具有超越纯粹计算的应用的人，并发表了第一个打算由这台机器执行的算法。因此，她有时被认为是第一个认识到“计算机”的全部潜力的人，也是第一批计算机程序员之一。洛夫莱斯是诗人拜伦勋爵和他的妻子安妮·伊莎贝拉·“安娜贝拉”·米尔班克夫人温特沃斯夫人唯一的合法孩子。拜伦的其他孩子都是非婚生子女。[6]拜伦在艾达出生一个月后和妻子分居，四个月后永远离开了英国。他用一首诗来纪念他们的分别:“你的脸像你母亲的脸吗?我美丽的孩子!”艾达!我的家和心的唯一的女儿?”中国英语学习网他在希腊独立战争中死于疾病，当时艾达8岁。她的母亲一直对她耿耿于怀，并鼓励艾达对数学和逻辑的兴趣，以防止她发展成她父亲眼中的疯子。尽管如此，艾达仍然对拜伦很感兴趣，在她最终去世时，应她的要求，她被葬在拜伦的旁边。她小时候经常生病。艾达于1835年嫁给威廉·金。1838年，国王被任命为洛夫莱斯伯爵，艾达因此成为洛夫莱斯伯爵夫人。
 </string>
</resources>